Ana Bollain

Front-end Developer





About me

Curious by nature, I define myself as persevering and resourceful. With great adaptability, my empathy, collaborative attitude and commitment make me a great team player.

Thanks to over 6 years of work experience in France and Spain, communicating in both english and french, I have mastered both project planning and stress management to meet client expectations with tight deadlines.

Soft skills

Teamwork
Empathy
Problem Solving
Attention to detail
Creative Thinking
Responsiveness
Adaptability
Management

Proyectos

Rick & Morty CD
Personal Project | React JS

Minion's Cards CD
Team Project | Javascript

Legacy JS Code Upgrading
Team Project | React & Node JS

Adalabers 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Whack Tartalo 👄 Personal Project | Javascript

Work Experience



Front-end Developer

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- > Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- > Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA application with React.
- > Developing a basic REST API with Node JS and Express JS.
- > SQLite for creating and managing databases and EJS Template Engine.
- > Version control with Git.
- > Project development under SCRUM framework and Agile philosophy.
- > Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Zeplin.
- > Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github, Railway.

Partner Architect & Freelance Interior Designer

Freelance. Remote | March 2022 - Oct. 2022 Estudi Biga SCCLP. Barcelona | Sept. 2019 - March 2022 Katty Schiebeck. Barcelona | April 2019 - Oct. 2019

- > Management and development of projects as a team leader.
- > Coordination of all parties involved for project decision-making.
- > Design, illustration and 3D rendering of creative proposals.
- > Production of techinal and administrative documentation.
- > Adaptabilty to **tigtht deadlines** with **high quality** standards.

Architect & Interior Designer

Atelier du Pont. Paris | Jan. 2017 - March 2019 AWP. Paris | March 2016 - Oct. 2016

- > Contact with clients in oral presentations and project follow-up.
- > Analysis of commercial proposals and compliance with client's budget.
- > Contact with sales representatives for the prescription of materials.
- > Management and development of residential and hospitality projects.

Education

Intensive Front-end Development Bootcamp

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

Online Web Development Courses

Platzi | Remote | July 2022 - Sept. 2022 HTML5 & CSS3 | CSS Grid | Javascript | JS Engine (V8) & Browser

Basics of Web Development & Coding

Coursera. University of Michigan | Remote | April 2022 - June 2022

Master of Architecture

Technical Skills

ETSAM. Polytechnic University of Madrid | Sept. 2008 - July 2015

Architecture & Landscape Exchange Program

KTH. Sweden | Erasmus | Sept. 2012 - July 2013

Spanish Native English Sass Professional, C1 Advanced (CAE) French Fluent SQLite **Basque**

Languages

Native, EGA